Hello welcome to Yo Stucks.
My name is Vikas and I will be with you on your show for the next 1 hour
and
we will talk [music] about your shares.
Whatever the confusion is, we will try to solve it
and in this effort,
a special guest will be with us, Ajit Mishra
of Railier Broking will be joining us shortly.
Before that, let's do one thing
[music] first, let's tell you
how you can join the show?
How can I send my questions?  Then you will see a QR code
flashing on your screen.
Scan this QR code and send
your question to us easily and quickly by scanning [Music].
Apart from that, you can see a number just below it,
9167329108. In
case you are not able to scan the QR code, then
call,
WhatsApp, message on this number and
send your question to us.  Apart from this, all the
social media handles will appear on your screen.  There's
Facebook, Twitter,
Instagram, and also YouTube
[music] live stream where you
can post your questions and
send them to us.  So
start sending your questions as soon as possible through all these social media handles.  Before your question comes, let's
check the market to see what is happening in the market at the
moment.  See, a
decline of 150 points is being seen in Nifty.  The
three-day rally has
finally been halted.  Today Sussex falls by 600 points
in Nifi Bank.  However, if you
look closely, you will see flat trading.  A
rise of around 25 points will be
seen there.  The villain of today's market is
IT shares.
You will see Nifty IT trading down by 4.5% at this time
and the reason for this is that the
results of IT companies and especially the guidance that is coming out have been
a bit disappointing
and due to which you can see that the
share of HCL Tech has fallen by 10.5%.
Pressure is also being seen on Tata LXI shares today.
You see, all the IT shares like Tech
Mahindra CFOs BIT Infosys, LTI My TCS are
seeing a decline.  TCS should
fall by 3%.  If a stock like Tech Mahindra HCLT
falls by 5 to 10%, then the index is
bound to fall by 4.5% and since
IT has a very high weightage in our overall
market, it has dragged the market downwards.
Let's
try to understand where we are getting some support from.  The
market is getting some support
from FMCG and energy counters and some defense
but that support is not enough and that is
why the market is down by 150 points.  Let's go to our
guest.  Ajit Mishra ji has
now joined us
from Really Broking.  Ajit ji, you are most welcome
to ET House Swadesh and thank you very much for
taking out the time.  Ah, what is your stance on the market
?  Today we are down 150 points. Nifty
IT is a cult, it is the biggest
villain in a way.  What is
your view on Nifty Bank, Nifty and IT
stocks?
Thank you Vikas.  See Vikas, this is the third
week where the market tone, till yesterday,
we were seeing that it was largely positive. Today, no doubt,
we are trading with a cut of half a percent,
but if you
see, the tone has remained on the positive side.
In between, we see that there is
a pause, a line for some region and the other in the index, like
today the IT crisis is definitely visible,
but largely the participation has been very
strong in this entire recovery, not
only from the index heavy weights but
also from the broader market. You have seen a recovery of
around 13 to 15% from the bottom in mid-cap and small-cap as well.
So looking at all these
things, I feel that there is still
room in the market for further upside.
If I talk about the index, then
like 24600, a level was tested yesterday, if it crosses
24800 where the long term
averages are placed,
I feel that the market still has the potential to go up to there.
Today IT is definitely on the back foot.  But at the
same time banking is holding quite strongly.  The
banking index had
surpassed the resistance levels of 57100 in the last trading
session, so we are seeing that the
strength is still there and the anticipation is
that its strength will help the
index and in taking this recovery forward,
means banking can play an important role in the 24800 that we are talking about.
Look at IT, we have talked about it a long
time ago that the
signs of underperformance there are quite evident.
In case of Means Recovery, your
participation is negligible and when there is a fall,
you are the first to fall and the most.
So this is a clear sign of under
performance.  So you should definitely
stay away from IT.  And your view is short term.
Definitely a position on the short side
as An One Market offers you.  You
can consider it.  But aggressive positioning in the long term should
not be done at least at these current levels when it comes
to the IT.  And
[nasal sound] the indication is
that in the second sensitive, like the auto
was just on the side lines, you might
see good traction there.  Metal
Energy Counters.  So bearing IT largely
and all sectors will be seen on strong footing.
So, you should use the occasional consolidation phase
for accumulation in the
strong sectors.
Absolutely.  So this opinion is on the overall market,
on Nifty Nifty Bank and on all the IT
stocks.  Let's go ahead
and have our first caller join us.  Let's
connect with them and talk to them.
Aniket Sarkar is associated with us.
Hi Aniket.  Good afternoon.  Tell me which
stock do you want advice on?
Hi.  Yes, I have 900 shares of ICICI
Lombard General Insurance.
I need feedback on what I've bought for the long term.
Ok.  The quantity you have is 900 and the
entry price is 1800.  Ok?
Yes,
okay.  Let's take some advice on this.
Ajit ji, he has ICICI Lombard.
He has bought 900 shares at the price of Rs 1800.   There is a
little long term view and the current prices are of
1823.  I think he
bought them around this time.
He bought it around this time.  What
will be your perspective?
Look, no doubt, Validity has a lot of experience in the insurance space
across life insurance and general
insurance counters but ICICI GI has a
comparatively better structure.  Meaning, you
saw a retracement from the record high,
from around 2200 you came to the levels of 1680 and as far as
I can see,
in the last one and a quarter years, you are seeing trading in the same band from 2000 to 1600
because their buying price is
near the current levels.  There is a long term view.
I think it should remain that way.  As of now the
1600 level is holding.  Till now
no major damage is visible
in the structure.  The overall consolidation will
remain with a positive bias.  The actual growth will happen
around 2050.  In that case,
you will again see the stock moving towards a new high.
So right now the opinion would be to hold
for long term with a stop loss of 1600.
You have to hold for now with a stop loss of 1600.
You are getting this opinion.
Let's move ahead.  Another caller has now
joined us.  Himanshu is associated with us.
Himanshu, welcome to ITO
Swadesh.  Hi, tell me which stock do you
want advice on?
Sir,
how many shares of SML Mahindra do you have?   I have
10 shares.
Good sir.  It is priced at Rs 4200.
Yes sir.  Yes sir.
Ok.  How many days can you keep it?   There is
no problem for a month or two.   A
month or two.  Ok?  So short term
is the only perspective.  Ajit ji, he has
shares of SML Mahindra.  There are 10 shares.  He has bought it at the price of Rs 4200.
Running around 3800.  A
correction of around 10% has already
come from where they bought.  And
even today the stock is trading 5% down.  The
results that came were not good.  The
streets did not like it well.
What is your stance?  What do you say?  What
should they do?  This is a one or two month perspective.
Absolutely, if you look at the development,
you will see a very strong bullish trend, like the rally that you saw from 1000 to 5000
in the stock, now for the
last four months we are seeing
that this tone of consolidation has come in the stock
and if it breaks the level of 3700, then
according to me, your short term bias will
change from positive to
sideways and maybe even negative, so according to me,
they should not continue the long position below 3700
because they have a
view of one to two months and
in the above case, you may see this stock resting at one time from 4200 to 4400 which is their
buying price zone.
So,
you will see it in the range of Rs 3700 to Rs 4400.  So
unless there is a decisive close
above the upper band, there
is no indication of any significant momentum here.  So it would be better
that if any recovery comes then
utilize it to reduce the position and at the
same time maintain a stop loss of Rs 3700.
Ok.  You must maintain a stop loss of Rs 3700 on
this.  This advice is being given to you Himanshu ji.
Okay, Nitesh ji has joined us as the next caller.
Nitesh ji, welcome
to EOZ.  Tell me which stock do you want advice on
?
Sir, I have bought 175 pieces of units from RBI,
171 175 175, I have
bought it at 380, should I hold it
or withdraw it?
Ok.  He has bought 175 shares of RVNL Rail Vikas Nigam Limited
at the price of Rs 380.  Currently
running around 380 and 302.  The loss has been
considerable.  Ajit ji, what should be done?
When will their prices return to 380
?
Look at the development, recently again
we have seen that there was good traction in the railway counters last
week and after that a
pause is being seen.  The good thing so far is
that there has been no price wise correction in this entire pause.
Time wise correction means
you are seeing these stocks trading in a small range.
So I think
this time there is a potential to make a decisive attempt.
If this stock of RBNL is able to go above 315,
then you can try to
bring it to its buying price.
If once 315 is broken,
then you can assume the potential to be in about two to
three months
[nasal sound] because this
is a high beta counter, so it can retest those levels.
Once it reaches 380,
definitely it will need to be reviewed.
In the interim, I would say keep
a stop loss of 290 in mind
because if it goes below that again, then it will become
range bound.  Then time will be
wasted.  So basis that
holds for now.  But on the rise, think about reducing it a little bit.   If there
is a surge, then
you should reduce the quantity a little and definitely place a stop loss of 290
because below that,
selling may increase.  Let this advice come to you from
Ajit ji.  Our next caller is
not an infact caller.  Our next viewer
is someone who is watching us on YouTube and
he has posted his question there.
Tapan has 60 shares of PFC.
He bought it at the price of Rs 385.
Running around 471.  There is a decent profit.
Ajit ji, should I leave?   Are you making a decent
profit or should I
hold on now and make a profit?
See Tapan ji, if you have taken it for short term
then you have traded at very good levels
and are currently making good profits.  The
stock is very close to its record high.
You can definitely book some profit here.
Because the move that has come is almost
vertical.  Means from 390 to 480,
almost if you see, there is a complete vertical rise.
So there could be a little bit of consolidation.  There may be a
slight pause.  So book at least
partial profit.
Maintain a trailing stop loss at 455
for the remaining position and if the zone of 520 530
comes then you should completely book a bar there
if the view is short
term
then if the view is short term then you are
making a good profit.  You have
got very clear advice from Ajit ji.
Follow this.  Let's move ahead and
we have to stop here for a short break.  We're looking forward to
more of your questions and calls when we return from the break.
We'll talk to you [music].  Will
take your questions and get
advice from Ajit ji.  But after a short break.
[Music]
Welcome back
to Your Stocks after the break, and we're continuing to cover all your questions.
And
now the next question we have
comes from YouTube itself.  Gautam ji has sent the question.
He has asked a question on Map My India.
Want this opinion on Map My India share.
A CE Info Basically CE Info
Systems Map My India A is
trading around Rs 937.  He
bought it at Rs 1093.  So there is some loss.
Ajit ji, what would be your advice?
He has purchased Map My India CE Info System for Rs 1093.  The current
price is Rs 937.  There is a loss of Rs 78000.
See, development has suffered a very sharp decline.
If you look at it from 1700, it took
very less time to reach 800.  Since then there has been an
attempt at a recovery rebound but it is not that decisive.
Means volume is your missing.  No
doubt currently we are seeing that the
stock is trying to hold its 20 EMA.
So, somewhere
this recovery of one attempt may get extended and
levels of around 1000
may be seen in the near term.  So according to me, instead of incurring a
huge like you know loss, it is better that
you maintain a stop loss of 900.
Now in case of further recovery once
000 comes near 20 then reduce the position once.
Let's go ahead and here is the feedback
you get on MAM India CE Infosist.
Let's move ahead now.  Let's
focus on one stock.  Suntech RT shares are
seeing a rise of 8% today.
What is the reason for the spectacular rise?  Our colleague Ravindra Digari has done complete research on this.
Ravindra, tell me what is the reason due to which
this tremendous growth is being seen?   Yes,
absolutely, here in Suntech Realty, a
lot of growth is being seen in today's session.
On intraday basis,
this stock is seeing a rise of more than 12%.  The
reason behind this is that the company released earnings for Q4 FI 26 and FI
26.
Although the financial performance
was in line with street estimates, the
presales and collections
of the company were quite strong.  Here, first of all let
us talk about revenue and PAT, a
good growth was seen in revenue and PAT on yearly basis.  There was a
growth of 65% in revenue.  At the same time, a
growth of 26% was seen in the profit.
However, the company reported revenue here
at Rs 339.  Jack Street was
estimating even higher revenue of Rs
400 crore.  Now let's talk about presales and
transactions which are very important
in real estate sector companies.  So, in Q4 FI26,
presales have seen a growth of 22%
and sections have also
seen a good jump of 39%
and the reason behind this is strong
execution here and the company has expanded its portfolio in the MMR region.
Due to this, a good growth was seen in pre-sales and collections
here.
Talking about FI 26, the guidance of the company for presales in FI 26
was Rs 3000 crore and the
actual presales reported by the company in FI 26 was Rs
3157 crore, which means the company has achieved
presales more than the guidance
and the growth has also been quite good, there has been a
growth of 25% on yearly basis.
Talking about the sections, in the sections also, a
very good
growth of 14% has been seen in FI 26.  Ah, in the net
cash flow surplus also, ah, a
good amount of growth was seen here.
Here the net cash sir ah net cash flow has
seen an increase of 48% on yearly basis to Rs 552 crore.
And finally, we will talk about FI
26, in FI 26 the company has expanded its
MMR development pipeline
through three strategic additions.
Whose combined estimated GDV is
approximately Rs 5000 crore.  So
due to a very strong set of presales and collections, Centec Realty is
seeing a rise of more than 12% on intraday basis.
Intraday saw a rise of up to 12% and
is still up around 8%.  This stock is
showing excellent growth.  Ah, it is necessary to get an opinion on this.
8% up now.
What else, if you see the performance,
this stock has risen by 28-29% in the last one month.
Ajit ji, what will be your opinion
on this particular share?  28 29% has
climbed this month.  However, if we
look at the yearly returns, it will still
appear negative.  7-8% but in the last 1 month a
run up of 28% has been seen.
What strategy should one have if one has it in the portfolio?
Vikas is considered a very volatile stock.
Considering that if you
look at the past, there have been very extreme
swings in stock prices.
For example, from 500 you bought the stock
in 2020 to 150, after that the recovery happened and
new highs of 575 were made and then again 250 and then
record highs when you made near 600
and then again 250, so
you know this stock has experienced extreme volatility since
listing, according to me
[sound of clearing throat] this recovery should be
used as an opportunity to
reduce your position because there is
resistance at multiple levels from 390 to 400
on multiple time frames.  So, by
utilizing this as a better opportunity, those
who have stuck positions should
think about exiting.  Also maintain
a stop loss in the interim between 300 to 390 to 400.  According to
me,
stop loss should be maintained near the level of 350.
We should maintain stop loss around 350.
This is my opinion on this stock.  It has been a very
volatile counter.  Let's move ahead
and our next viewer has
sent us a question through social media,
Vinod Mehta ji, Vinod Mehta ji has
Tata Power.  Not to mention Tata Power is
making new 52 week highs every day.   Every
day we see the market opening every morning.
Tata Power makes new 52 week high.
Ah quantity he has is 2500 shares.
Buying is interesting.  He bought it for ₹200.  The
price is ₹438.  It has more than doubled.
Ok.  Now I have earned a
good amount of money.  But let's check once whether we can
earn more money.  Ajit ji, this stock is making new 52 week highs almost every
day.
Entry is at the price of Tata Power 200.  Great
entry price.  So they are making a good profit
because they have 2500 shares
in quantity.  What should be done?
Now should some profit booking be done on these at this
level or should we just hold them tight for now?
See, Vikas is a very low level buy
and this indicates that he is a long term
investor.  If there
is no consolidated position in just one stock then definitely there
is still no reason to exit this stock
because
this move is coming after a long consolidation correction of one and a half years.
So according to me it will not fizzle out so soon.
In the next leg, you see the
potential to retest the record highs. The
potential to retest the levels of 475-480 is visible in the near term
and if it breaks out from there then you will
see a new treasury being formed, so
according to me you should stay put for now, if by any
chance you have a consolidated position then
you should definitely book a little bit.
You can think about investing in other stocks near 470-75.
Ok?  So this is a clear opinion about Tata
Power.  Now let's go to our next caller Sukanya Sukanya
Dutta with us.
In fact, he has sent the question to us
through social media only.
His question is on Raymond Limited.  The quantity is 3000 shares
and the entry price is Rs 602.
Their entry price is Rs 602 on Raymond.  The current
prices are around 452.
Raymond has suffered a substantial loss.
From here, their loss is around ₹150 per share.
The quantity is also fine.  What
should be done Ajit ji?  He bought it at 452, the
current price is 452 and he bought it at 602.
Absolutely, the damage is quite extensive.  The
fall which started from 800,
took the stock to 300.  A very
strong recovery has been seen this month.  Means from what
I can see we have posted gains of around 40%
this month.  And the
indication is that the momentum may carry a little more.
Above 480, you can assume
levels of around 500-520, but by the time it reaches there,
I think
you might see the stock pausing and then there could be a
consolidation phase.  So my
advice would be to stay put for now
with a stop loss of 420.  At least
they should be considered now.  Because if it
goes below those levels then you will have to
face the pressure again.  And review
your position once again near 500 520.
You should review your position again around 500-520.  There has been a
lot of decline.  There has been a
lot of loss.  I think
if you had asked the question a little earlier,
your loss might have been a little less.  This show is
for you.  Your stocks
move according to you.  It works only on the questions you send.
So don't hesitate to send your questions.
Well, for now,
we have to end this segment of the show here.
But your questions will
not stop.  We'll take more of
your questions and calls when we return after a short break.
Another guest will
join us.  For now, thank you very much Ajit ji.
You joined and
gave your advice on various stocks [music].
Let's stop here for a short break.
More of your questions and
their answers with another guest after the break.
[Music]
Hello, welcome back to Your Stucks,
and we ca
n't stop taking your questions [Music].  Your
questions will continue for the next
half an hour.  How can you join?
How can I send my questions?  First of all you will
see a QR code flashing on your screen.
You have to scan this QR code
and by scanning it you
can send your questions to us [music].
Apart from that, a number
is visible below the QR code in your screen 9167329108,
you can also send us your questions here.
If you want to connect with us through social media
, want to send us questions,
then you can ask us your questions by posting them in the comment box on all these handles like
Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and
also on the live stream of YouTube.
We'll be covering these questions on the show
and getting opinions from our experts who
join us
so you can get the right opinion at the right time [music].
Kunal Parar of Choice Equity Brooking will join us shortly.
Before we welcome them.  Let's
take a little bit of a Czech market [music].  Let's
also ask about the market.  Look, the
market is down today.  The three-day
rally has come to a halt.
You will see a weakness of 160 points in Nifty 50.  It
is about 12% weak.  Sussex was trading up
650 points and Nifty Bank was also trading flat.
Now the mild negative
seems to be going into the territory.
Fall of 30 points.  But the biggest
weakness in the market today has come
from IT shares.  Nifty IT is down almost 5% today
and the reasons for that fall are
weak guidance, weak commentary,
weak outlook and weak results of HCLT.
HCLT is down 10.5%.  In today's trading, the
weakness in Tata LXI is also around 5%
and both these stocks have
spoiled the mood in the market a bit.
Even in Persistent, the weak
business is being seen today with weakness.
Now look, all the Nifty IT stocks, even the
biggest giants like TCS, are down by at least 2 to 3%.
And the biggest
decline is in HCLT.  A drop of around 10.5%
on your screen.
Leave aside OFSS, you will see all the
IT stocks trading weak today.
OFSS which
is also strong has weakness of around half a%.   It
is difficult to predict when it will turn negative.  Apart from this,
you see that the strength that has come today is
in FMCG shares.
Enstle is leading the strength of FMCG stocks.  Nestle's
results were good.  After that
came the bullish outlook of brokerages.  His reports came.
Targets were increased and you can see its impact
on the installation.  Yesterday also, the FMCG
index closed around 4%
higher than the FFCG
index and the pull towards the upwards was
done by NSTL itself.  So you
see, even today, whether it is Tata Consumer,
Emami, HL, Varun Berges, Nestle,
DAB, GZ Consumer, a rise of 2 to 5% is being
seen in these cities today, so
this is the overall condition of today's market.  Now let's have
our special guests join us.  Let's
welcome him once.
Ask him what his opinion is on the market?   We have
Kunal Parar with us from Choice Equity Booking.
Kunal ji, you are very welcome
to 18 House Swadesh.  Thank you very much for
taking the time.  The first perspective I
want to take is your market.  There is a weakness of 150 points.
Which way do you see the market going?
Will the decline increase further by the time of closing
?
Well good afternoon sir.  Well, for now the market has
managed to hold itself together.  It is
around 24,400.  The view here is on the positive
side only.  Any decline occurs.
I feel that at the present level of
24,380 or 24,350, I would say that it would be advisable to
initiate a long position there and then proceed further.
The way
we are seeing momentum in the stock here, the
lower level of 24300 in the particular index
is a very good support, the chances of it being broken are
less at the moment.  Talking about OP level,
24,500 is a very good
resistance today.  No doubt yesterday
we got a closing above 24,500 but it did not sustain today.
So if the market sustains today
or if it sustains in the coming days,
then
Nifty can show you levels up to 24,500.  The overall
view here regarding Nifty is on the positive
side.  If I
see a correction of 2030 points, then it would be advisable to
maintain a position here with an SL of 24300.   It would be
advisable to maintain the position from here with a stop loss of Rs 24,300.
Kunal ji's view on Nifi is positive and you can see that the
support at 24,300 is also looking quite good.
If you talk about resistance, then
strong resistance is being
seen in Nifty at 24,500.  If you
look at the options data, well, at least you have a
view on the market.  Our first
caller who has now joined us is
Ashish ji.  Ashish ji, good afternoon, welcome to
your Instagram page.  Tell me which stock do
you want advice on?
No friend, the problem was to
ask about BST, I have 125 shares and am
purchasing it for 925, I am a long term investor, sir, I wanted to
ask that I want to hold it, what all should be done,
you bought it at 925, the price has reached 3500,
Ashish ji, by looking at the price we
can tell you that you are a long term
investor.  Well, whatever long term
investors join us, we
always show them and tell the rest of the viewers
that
if you want to create wealth, then long term
investment is the best way.
And look, this
is visible to you as an example.  He bought it at Rs 925 and now the
price has reached Rs 3500.  So you can understand the
level of long term wealth creation that has happened due to this.
Look, the
money has increased four times, which means around Rs 3500.  Now
Ashish ji's question is whether to hold
it further or the matter has been settled now.   There has been
so much progress.  We should leave now.
Kunal ji, what will be your opinion?  The
price has reached Rs 3500.  He bought it at Rs 925.   The
view here is to hold the position and
move ahead for now.  It is around 3515.
His purchase is for Rs 925.  That means it was a purchase made a year or two ago.
We can say this and go ahead.   The
overall view is on the positive side.  It
is advisable to maintain your position while walking.
In the coming days,
this stock can show levels ranging from 3800 to 4100.  And if there is such a
good level of buying then I
would say that you should convert it for ultra long term.
Because
many times what happens is that if the stock
becomes 2x or 3x then people leave from there and
take profit.  Capital is also taken away.
But actually
we get to see its momentum only after that.
So I would say that you should hold on to it,
you may see levels from 3800 to 4100
in the coming days.
Hey Kunal ji, you have introduced a new word
today – ultra long term.
When Gaurang Sir joins us, he says
that when I say long term, then
consider it to be minimum 12 to 15 months and if you consider it to be an
average, then it would be 3 to 5 years.  Now tell me
how ultra long term is this?
Well, if you shift in the ultra long term,
normally sir, what happens is that whenever we do
choice working or whenever we come,
we focus a lot on generational wealth,
that wealth is such a wealth which is
also very beneficial for your future generations.
You get the advance advantage
and normally what happens is that there is a
long term view like brother 2
years, 3 years, 4 years, 5 years, ultra
long term is such that it becomes
your view for more than 10 years also.   That
means you can carry it even after 10 years.
And normally what happens is
that every stock has a cycle of 7 years
and there are some stocks which
go up to 3x 4x 5x in a cycle of 7 years,
after that there is a little side and after that
you get to see a good momentum there
and you see sir, all the
stocks, all the stocks, talk about Bajaj
Finance, talk about Infosys,
talk about Bajaj Fins, there are
many such stocks which have given
very good returns in a period of 10 years,
even after that the stock has
shown us a rally, so in view of this, I would
say that buy and hold it at a very good level.
Two-three years, no doubt, that's your
viewpoint.  You hold it and go.
But I would say that you should
take it for the ultra long term.  The stock may
show you another level of returns.  Which
you will neither see in FD
nor in the trading
you do.  So
if I were to say living examples of this, there are stocks like Bajaj Finance,
Bajaj Fins, Infosys
which have earned a good amount of wealth for our
investors.
Absolutely right, it is right and
Kunal ji has a lot of conviction on BSE and
ultra long term, if you
want to understand how the benefits are, then you must have
seen those stories on social media in
which some particular investor
tells the viewer that he has found
an old share certificate of Reliance,
MRF or any other company, the money has
now increased a lot, then that is an
ultra long term story.
So you should identify this kind of story
and invest in it.  Let's go to our
next caller Gaurav who is joining us
from Sonipat Haryana.  Gaurav ji, you are very
welcome to 18 House Saresh.  Tell me which
stock do you want advice on?
Hello sir.  My name is Gaurav.  I have
GAIL shares at 177 for 500 shares and for one year.
What should I do now?
You bought it for Rs 177.  166 is running.
You have bought 500 shares at exactly ₹11 below where you bought them.  There is some
loss.  Let's ask
Kunal ji once.  Kunal ji, please tell me about this Gayle,
sir, it is running at 166.
He bought it at Rs 177.  There is some loss.  Are you
sitting on hold or would
you also advise a little averaging?   That
means if it is purchased around Rs 175 then
it is a purchase made before November 2025.  And
if I talk about dividend, the
stock has also declared a dividend of ₹5 on 5th February.  That
means the benefit of dividend has
definitely been received.  It would be advisable to
hold the existing position for now.
As soon as 172 172 is broken,
you can see levels up to 195 here.
Now here I would like to tell Vikas one
thing that G is fundamentally a very
good stock.  It is a good dividend
paying stock.  But what happens here is that
if you want to play a long term story, then
whenever such stocks make a lower bottom,
if they reach 52 week low or
you can say that they reach six month low, then you have to
add a position there and go.
Because lower averages will be a
biggest threat ever for this kind of
counter which is fundamentally good but does
not perform that well but which
investors want to create wealth.  So
you should hold the existing position
and I would definitely say that if there is
any decline in the stock from here
up to the level of 142, then it would be
advisable to add the position there also
because there is a good bottom for the stock.
In the coming days,
you may see levels up to 198-200 in the market.
So if it stays above 172 then
levels up to 198-200 can be seen.
This opinion on Gayle is from Kunal ji.  Okay, the next
caller is connected with us from Gaya and our
caller Dilip ji, Dilip Kumar Jain ji is
connected from Gaya.  Dilip ji, welcome to
AT Sandesh.  Tell me which stock do
you want advice on?
I have it.
Which shares are you sir?   There
are 120 shares at the price of ₹1000.   Do
you have electric shares?
No, right now I had a query from the Midwest.
Midways
or
Midvas Sir, please tell me once, which Midwest
share are you talking about?  Midways
Midwest Limited
Midwest MID W S
OK You are talking about the shares of Midwested.
When was this share listed?  Let's
see this once first.  Midwest Limited, yes there is a
share, its price is around 1323 on NSE.
But look Dilip ji, this
is out of our coverage list.  So
we will not be able to give you an opinion on this, but if
you want advice on any other stock, then I can get
you an opinion on that stock.
I will give it to you once on Snyder.   Yes of course.
So Sider Electric has 120 shares.
They have an entry price of around Rs 1023 and apart from Sider Electric, if
you look at Sider Electric, the
prices are now around Rs 1111.  Kunal
ji, what would be your opinion on Sider Electric
?
Well sir, if we talk about side electric, the view regarding side
electric is currently on the positive
side.  The stock is up 5% today.  Its
previous top of 1055 has also been crossed by the stock.
We can see a good rally from here.  Where
as soon as 1180 and 1180 are broken,
you can see levels up to 1260 also.   The
overall view is definitely on the positive side.
Regarding Sidders Electric.
Definitely the positive side is the pay view.
Regarding Sider Electric.  Let's now
move on to our next viewer.
Mahendra Kumar Agarwal ji is associated with us
and in fact he has sent his question
through social media.  A question
is about LNT.  He has 100 shares.
Another long term investor is with us.
Now this means an entry price of 1150
above their LNT.  So it seems like a very old buying to
me.
Kunal ji will tell us at what time LNT 1150 would have gone.  Kunal ji has
bought 1150 L&T. Prices are hovering around Rs 4000.
What should they do?
1150 means please understand sir, this is about 2020.
Where LNT once looked at the lower level, it had
also made a low of around 800.
After that we saw a one way rally in L&T.
I would say that instead of
booking profits in this stock, it is better to
continue it for the long term.  Because
you will not get this average back in the coming days
and if once
we exit this stock then you will not get this entry price back
and the return that you
want, the return that you want to see
psychologically, you will not see that return, so
you should open the existing position and go ahead, on the
basis of ongoing Iran and US conflict,
we saw a good correction in the stock
but there is nothing to worry about,
in the coming days it
can reclaim its old level of 4400
and this time if 4400 is crossed then
you can also see levels up to 48800 here.
Now Vivek ji, one
thing that happens here is that the entry is around Rs 1100.  The
stock is trading at the level of 4000.
That means Four X Capital has been done.
Now, from here, whatever the stock
rises, it will rise only to show the level
because the returns that are being received have already been
received and good returns can also be received.  The
level is just
for show.  It is to tell.  Actually, more
cream can be seen in the coming days,
particularly
in counters like LAT.  We can definitely see further rise in
prices up to 4800.  This
opinion is from Kunal ji.  Let's have our
next caller join us live now.
Nitin Kumar is associated with us
from Roorkee.  Nitin ji, welcome to our house.
Tell me which stock do you want advice on?
Sir, I have a question on Aditya Infotek.  I
bought the shares at ₹157.  The
quantity is 250.
Ok.  You have bought it at the price of Rs 1057.   Yes yes.
Ok?  Meaning their buying is around 52 week low.
105 is the 52 week low.
Here is Aditya info.  This is the code for CP Plus.
Its code is CP Plus basically and
now the share price has gone above 2200.
That means the money has doubled.
What to do in Aitya Infot?
Now Kunal ji, what advice will you give?
Well, today's show is going to be very memorable for me
because among all the
queries that have come, somewhere or the other they have increased the
capital 2x 3x.  Aditya Infotek
is also one such stock.
His purchases are around Rs 1057.  Currently the stock is
around 2212.  In the coming days, this stock is ready to
show levels of 2530 and the day it breaks 2530, it is ready to show levels up to 3200.
Based on the overall momentum theory, this
stock is trading at an all-time high.
Moving into uncharted territory.  And
whenever such momentum is seen,
technically the stock moves to even higher levels,
hence the advice here would be to
hold the existing position once and then
move ahead.   It would be
advisable to hold the existing position.  Let
us stop here for a short break with this query.
But after the break, we will include more of your questions
in this show.  A short break, come back
soon.
[Music]
After the break, welcome back to
Your Stucks, your own show,
and we're constantly including your questions in this show.
Now
we have received a question from Vikas Patil through social media.
He has bought shares of Power Grid.
He has 250 shares.  Their entry price is
₹104.  Wonderful.  Of ₹14.  Kunal ji, today it
seems that today is the day of long term
investors.
This is a purchase of 2019.  He has purchased Power Grid at ₹104.
What is your advice?  Stay seated and
hold on tight.
Well definitely Sir it is a purchase of around 104.  The
stock is trading around Rs 320.
And the best part is that this
stock is also a good dividend paying stock.
I think you see that PS comes under stock
and normally such stocks are
considered very good for giving dividend and
recently the stock has also given a dividend of ₹ 0.5 on
9th February.  So
they are also getting the benefit of dividend.  So the existing
position should definitely be held here.
And I would also like to say that
whatever dividend you get in this stock,
you can reinvest that dividend also in this particular
stock.  So what happens is that
your investment sale will become
active at a more robust level.  So it would be advisable to
hold this particular stock for now.
In the coming days,
as soon as 350 is broken,
you can see levels up to 380 here.
We are giving you this advice.  Let's move ahead.
Another viewer has
shared this question with us on social media.
Rahul is there.  Rahul Deshmukh has
bought Halco.  He has bought 180 shares
and the entry price is interesting here too.  The
interest entry price is ₹682.   Are
long term investors.  Saying
clearly
what should Halco do for long term portfolio?  He bought it at Halco for ₹682.  The
current price will be
above Rs 1000.  Yes, the
current prices are 1032.  The money has increased by around one and a half times.
Kunal ji, what should I do?  Today we have investors who have one and a half times, two times,
three times and four times their returns.
What should be done in HCO?
Well, in HCO the view is definitely on the positive
side.  There is uncertainty around 1032
which is becoming a
little stable here regarding the wall.
View: If we talk about the coming days here,
I feel that there is a
level up to 1300 which can be seen in Hindalo.
And if 1300 is broken then
you can see even better momentum there.  The
overall view is on the positive side.
Here it would be advisable to hold the position and
move ahead.
We absolutely.  So this advice is on Hindalco.
Now with this the time limit is coming to an
end.  So first of all we have to thank Kunal ji a lot.
Thank you very much Kunal ji.  Today you joined and gave advice on many shares
and especially on those shares which are
long term investment shares
where three-four times returns have been made.
Thank you very much Kunal ji.
Let's go ahead and
take a look at what's happening in the FAO market
?  His too.  You bring the prices of Nifty futures of FAO Nifty.  Let's take a
look at what is happening in the futures and options
market.  Get Nifty
50 futures first on your screen.
See, there is a discount of ₹4
on Nifty futures at this time.
Open interest has increased by around half a percent.  But the
spot prices are almost down.  Let's
get Nifty Bank futures.  Ah, the
trend there too is
going opposite to the market.  See, the discount is
around ₹16.  NFT Bank
Future Ah, this is the future of April 28th.
Open interest has fallen slightly here.   Please
show the spreads of NFT Bank once.   Let us
guess what is going on in the banks.
So you see HDFC Bank is
seeing new short builds.  ICICI
Bank new shorts are visible to you.
You are seeing some new long builds happening in Axis Bank.
But today you can see new shorts being made in all the big banks be it
ICICI, HDFC or SBI.   There
is some mixed business and
because of that, if you look at Nifty Bank, it is remaining
flat.  It is becoming flat to negative
or sometimes even flat to positive.
So this is the situation of Nifty Bank.  Go ahead
and bring some OI change.  Let's take a look at NFT 50 to see
where most of the action is happening.
See, 24,400 and 24,500 are the two
levels where maximum action is being
seen in OI.  The maximum OI
change and open interest change is
happening at these two levels.  Let's talk about distribution.  From this, we can get an
idea of
where support and resistance are seen
in the market today.  You see,
if you look at the level of 24,400 in Nifi, you will see
support and resistance, basically both call sellers
and put sellers will be
seen fighting here at 24,400 and
what is above 24,400 is slightly above the
spot prices at this time,
but you see, the red line at 24,500 is
quite big, that means the resistance is quite
big around 24,500.  So this
picture is showing you the distribution of OI.
Let's take a look at some of the futures gainers to see
who are the gainers in the futures market today.
What IREDA is today is that it is
emerging as a gainer in the futures market.  ABB and XID Industries, these three will be seen as
futures gainers today.   Let us
talk about losers and see
which shares in the futures market are
in the category of losers.  HCL Tech
eyes weak results.  Tata Alexi weak results
impact Tata Tech Mahindra results are about to come.
But even before that, you can see
shorts building up in the futures market.  The
decline
is visible here.  There is weakness in all the IT counters today
and you will see that among the losers of futures, all the three
shares will be from the IT counter only.  Let's move ahead.
Open interest
brings gainers and losers to your screen.
Now see, the open interest has increased the most
in Tata LXI.  New shots are building
and 27% open interest is
seen increasing.  Look at Divi's Lab here,
open interest is seen increasing around 10%.
But long builds are happening here.
In the losers, you will see that
due to short covering, open interest is
decreasing in all three stocks.  There is Masgaon Dock,
Yes Bank and Cochin Shipyard.  There is a
rise in defence shares today
and its effect is visible in short covering.
So these open interest
losers are visible on your screen.
You should buy a put of 1300 on HCLT.  If
you look at the weakness in HCLT today, the spot
prices are now seen reaching around 1257.
You will see that on the put of 1300, there is a
good open interest addition of 8.5 lakh
shares.  85 lakh new contracts have been
added here and the share price is
seen falling.  Another putt
brings your name to the forefront.  Nestle brings to
you a call of 1400.  Nesle will
bring the call for 1400.  That's what this put.
If you buy Nesle's 1400 call, you will
realize that there has been a good amount of
open interest addition here too.  Ah, because
this stock is in a bullish trend.  All the
FSC FMCG counters are
trading with good momentum and
Nestle is showing a continuous bullish trend since the results came yesterday.
So this is the overall situation of FAO market at this
time.  12:30 Infact 1:00 PM FAO
update on what is happening in the FAO market.
Let us stop here for a short break.
When we return after the break, we will bring
you the stocks
quickly.
[music]